<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<jobActivity xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <activityDate>2019-07-17T12:49:45.9918922+01:00</activityDate>
  <createdOn>2019-07-17T12:50:58.1203275+01:00</createdOn>
  <modifiedOn>2019-07-17T12:50:58.1203275+01:00</modifiedOn>
  <title>initial history ...</title>
  <body>Hi Muhammet,

Thanks for the connection. I thought I would drop you a message to introduce myself and see if you would be open to career opportunities in the next 12 months? I work on both contract and permanent roles across the UK and look to connect with and speak to people like yourself.

Muhammet Atalay sent the following message at 10:51 AM
View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  10:51 AM
Hello,

Thank you very much for your message 
I am looking for contract based opportunity. I will be available after 12 th July due to notice period. 

If you have any contract base opportunity I will be happy to talk to you.

Please be informed that I will be in London Saturday for 13 days in order to finalize procedures in home office UK so we can arrange a meeting to talk further :) if you do not mind.

Finally, keep in touch for even urgent start position . I can consider to start 2 or 3 hours a day till 12 th July from Istanbul immediately than continue full after 12th July .


I can send my updated cv if you share your email address.


Regards,

Muhammet ATALAY...

Harry Nicholson sent the following message at 10:55 AM
View Harry’s profile Harry Nicholson
Harry Nicholson  10:55 AM
 Hi Muhammet,

Thanks for your reply. I work a little different I like to prequalify all candidates before discussing roles with them, I currently don't have many contract roles available. I am based in Leeds so won't be able to meet in London I am afraid. If something comes up I will message you.

My email is harryn@montash.com

Thanks,
Harry

Muhammet Atalay sent the following message at 11:00 AM
View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  11:00 AM
 Perfect I will send my cv today for sure..,

Harry Nicholson sent the following message at 11:01 AM
View Harry’s profile Harry Nicholson
Harry Nicholson  11:01 AM
 Great, thanks

JUL 3
Muhammet Atalay sent the following message at 9:19 AM
View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  9:19 AM
 Hello,
hopes, this message finds you well.

I have come accross contract base Dynamics CRM position that you published in totaljobs.

Microsoft Dynamics 365 Developer (87019308) - https://www.totaljobs.com/job/dynamics-365-developer/montash-job87019308

if the position is still open, would you like to consider my CV that i sent before?

we can arrange a video conference, phıne call or even face2face meeting :) to discuss the position.

regards,

Muhammet ATALAY

JUL 8
Harry Nicholson sent the following message at 8:30 AM
View Harry’s profile Harry Nicholson
Harry Nicholson  8:30 AM
 Hi Muhammet,

This role has unfortunately been filled. However we can arrange a phone call to discuss your skills and experience, so going forward I can match roles you more closely.

Regards,
Harry

Muhammet Atalay sent the following message at 8:35 AM
View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  8:35 AM
 Hello Harry,

thanks for your message,

when shall we arrange a call ?  by the way, I am now in Istanbul for 2 weeks (vacation :) ) so there are 2 hours time differences between us.

regards,
Muhammet

Harry Nicholson sent the following message at 8:36 AM
View Harry’s profile Harry Nicholson
Harry Nicholson  8:36 AM
 Okay Muhammet. We can book in a call upon your arrival home in 2 weeks if better for you?

Muhammet Atalay sent the following message at 8:39 AM
View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  8:39 AM
 ok. sounds good. I will inform you once i am back. Is your mobile number valid : 07790862359 ?

Harry Nicholson sent the following message at 8:40 AM
View Harry’s profile Harry Nicholson
Harry Nicholson  8:40 AM
 Yes my number is correct.

Muhammet Atalay sent the following messages at 8:40 AM
View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  8:40 AM
 Okay, great

 Thank you

TODAY
View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  6:13 AM
 Hello Harry from London :)

Hopes, this message finds you well.

My i call you today at 10 am or would you like to suggest a timeslot based on your availability.

thanks a lot.

regards,

Muhammet ATALAY

Harry Nicholson sent the following message at 8:19 AM
View Harry’s profile Harry Nicholson
Harry Nicholson  8:19 AM
 Morning Muhammet, 

That is fine. Call the office on 0113 4830281 and if I can't answer then one of my colleagues either Jack or James will be best suited to have a phone call with you.

Kind Regards,

Harry

Muhammet Atalay sent the following messages at 9:58 AM
View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  9:58 AM
 Thanks, Harry

View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  10:03 AM
 I have just called you but you were at another call James was already in a call jack was not available:)

 I left a message to you

View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  10:05 AM
 This is my phone . +44 (0) 772 16 08 414

View Muhammet’s profile Muhammet Atalay
Muhammet Atalay  10:12 AM
 Regards
</body>
  <regarding />
  <contact>Harry Nicholson</contact>
  <type>LinkedIn Message</type>
</jobActivity>